What you're about to watch is a video of the Virgin Islands representative, Stacey Plaskett, a sister and a Democrat being fed by Jeffrey Epstein.
This was when Barack Obama was president of the United States.
And while we were once driving through a struggling neighborhood in Chicago, he commented that only black people could live that way.
Attorney Klein privilege, yes, I will turn it over.
You, as my friend, Mr. Meadows pointed out, misled this committee even today in a written submission that contradicted your testimony.
You have suggested you are going to review that.
Did you review it?
Are you going to review it in our next break to correct the record?
Yes or no?
Yes.
Question.
You helped out the president's campaign or were involved in the campaign as a representative, as a spokesman, even in your words today.
It was your idea for the campaign dating back to 2011.
Is that accurate?
Yes or no?
Yes.
Mr. Weisenberg and other individuals, Ms. Rona.
Who are those individuals?
Are they with the Trump Organization?
They are.
Are there other people that we should be meeting with?
So, Alan Weisenberg is the chief financial officer.
Uh-huh.
You've got to quickly give us as many names as you can so we can get to them.
Yes, ma'am.
As Ms. Rona, what is Ms. Rona's?
Rona Graff is Mr. Trump's executive assistant.
And would she be able to corroborate many of the statements that you've made here?
Yes, she was, her office is directly next to his and she's involved in a lot that went on.
I don't know how many ways I can say this to y'all, but these Democrats ain't your friend and I don't care what color is they skin.
The United States has an unbreakable bond with Israel.
Israel is a true friend.
It is our greatest ally in the region.
The International Criminal Court singles out Israel, but not Iran.
It's great to be here at the annual conference in support of the U.S.-Israel relationship.
A relationship that, of course, is anchored in our shared values.
Always also made clear that we continue to support Israel's right to defend itself.
Go.
expectations
Ahí.
Go.